Previously on the show. Paddi, who has a sprout growing on his head,
上集說到，頭上長出樹苗的懶羊羊
is responsible for making weather fruit.
要負責製造天氣果
His misunderstanding towards Weslie gave Wolffy a chance to take advantage of.
由於對喜羊羊的誤會 讓灰太狼有機可乘
After finding out the truth,
知道真相後的懶羊羊十分愧疚
Paddi felt guilty and made the weather fruit attack Wolffy.
製造天氣果擊敗了灰太狼
What will happen next?
接下來還會發生什麼呢？
"Flying Island: The Sky Adventure: The Fruits of Hardwork."
《奇幻天空島之》
What to do? Look at the condition of the weather tree.
怎麼辦？天氣樹現在變成了這樣
And there are so many orders!
而且，還有這麼多的訂單
Don't worry. Paddi and I will help out the best we can.
不用擔心 我跟懶羊羊一定會盡全力幫忙的
Paddi!
懶羊羊
Looks like he has a cold.
看來，他應該是感冒了
Doctor, we've noticed too.
醫生，我們也看出來了
But if you take your medicine on time, you'll be fine in no time.
不過，只要準時吃藥 感冒很快就會好的
Medicine? Doctor, I'm not sick!
吃藥？醫生我沒感冒啊
Look, I'm feeling great.
你看看，我還精神得很呢
Paddi, listen to the doctor and take your medicine.
懶羊羊，你就乖乖聽話吃藥吧
Exactly! You'll feel better afterward.
對啊，吃完病就好了
I don't want medicine!
我不要吃藥！
Doctor, I've caught a cold. Can you give me some medicine?
醫生，我感冒了，能給我開點藥嗎？
Just take this pill and your sickness will be gone in no time.
只要吃下這顆藥 你的感冒很快就會好的
I don't want medicine!
我不要吃藥啊
Paddi.
懶羊羊…
So amazing!
好神奇啊
Who knew my nose would clear up just after taking the medicine.
沒想到吃完藥 我的鼻子馬上就不塞了
The medicine is clearly very effective.
看來藥效還挺明顯的呢
Of course. If you take your medicine, you'll be fine in two days.
那當然了 只要按時服藥兩天就能痊癒了
Doctor, why didn't you say it earlier?
醫生，你怎麼不早點說呀？
But no worries, I'll go explain it to Paddi now.
不過沒關係 我現在就去跟懶羊羊解釋清楚
Paddi, I'm telling the truth.
懶羊羊，我說的是真的
This cold medicine is really effective!
這個感冒藥真的很有效啊
You'll recover very soon if you take it.
你吃了的話很快就會好的
Okay, fine.
好啦，我知道了
I need to sleep now. I'll take it later.
我現在要睡覺，等一下我就會吃的
Okay, rest first then.
好，那你先休息
I've put the pills on the table.
我把藥放在桌子上了
Remember to take it when you wake up.
你睡醒了之後記得吃喔
I'm not gonna take it.
我才不要吃呢
That patient had such a crazy reaction after taking it.
剛才那個病人吃完那麼大反應
Thinking of it makes me scared.
現在想起來都覺得可怕
How is Paddi doing?
懶羊羊情況怎麼樣了？
Looks like he's still unwilling to take it.
好像還是不太願意吃
Oh no, we're in trouble.
這下麻煩了
There are still 1,000 incomplete fruit orders.
還有一千個果實訂單沒有完成呢
And now Paddi is sick. What should I do?
懶羊羊現在又生病了 該怎麼辦才好呢？
How about I go explain to the customers,
要不我去跟客戶解釋一下吧
see if we can give them a partial order first?
看能不能先送一部分呢？
Fantastic!
不錯嘛
The weather fruit got here on schedule.
天氣果訂單這麼準時送到
How come there're so few?
怎麼這麼少呀？
I'm so sorry. There's a situation at the factory.
實在不好意思，工廠出了點意外
Please use these first.
這些您先用著
It's hard to keep my business going without enough weather fruits.
沒足夠的天氣果 我的店很難維持下去啊
My deepest apologies. We'll deliver the rest in two days.
對不起，剩下的這兩天我們盡快送到
Oh, I see.
這樣啊
Okay, you promised, two days.
好吧，那就兩天喔
Hello, is anyone there? I'm here to deliver the weather fruits.
請問有人嗎？我是來送天氣果的
Did you send the wrong package?
你是不是送錯了？
I ordered more weather fruits than this.
我訂的天氣果沒這麼少啊
I'm sorry, there's a problem at the factory.
不好意思，因為出了點意外
We'll deliver the rest in two days.
剩下的我們這兩天盡快送到
Mum... I want ice cream.
媽媽…我要吃冰淇淋
We don't have enough weather fruits now.
現在天氣果不夠
How about we have some in two days? I'll see you again.
我們過兩天再吃好嗎？你先去忙吧
I'll deliver the rest as soon as I can.
我會盡快把剩下的，送過來給你們的
I've finally dealt with the customers, for now.
總算暫時應付了那些客戶
But the rest needs to be produced in two days. What should we do?
可是剩下的要兩天內完成 怎麼辦啊？
Thank you, Weslie.
辛苦了，喜羊羊
I'll think of something for the rest.
剩下的我再想想辦法
Why don't you go check on Paddi?
你先去看一看懶羊羊怎麼樣了吧
I wonder if Paddi's cold recovered or not.
不知道懶羊羊感冒好點了沒有？
Turns out Paddi didn't take a single pill.
原來懶羊羊一片藥都沒有吃啊
Paddi, get up and eat candy.
懶羊羊，快起來吃糖果了
If you don't eat it, I will.
你要是不起來吃我就把它吃掉囉
No way. No reaction from him at all.
不會吧？這樣都沒反應
How refreshing!
好清涼啊
Turns out the pill is just like mint candy.
原來這糖像薄荷糖一樣的
Where did Paddi go?
懶羊羊去哪了？
Excuse me, have you seen a goat come here to buy snacks?
請問有看到一隻羊過來買零食嗎？
I haven't.
沒有啊
Have you seen a goat about this high and a little chubby?
有見過一隻大概這麼高 胖胖的羊嗎？
Paddi!
懶羊羊
Paddi, where are you?
懶羊羊，你在哪？
Are you looking for me?
你們是要找我嗎？
Sorry, wrong person.
對不起，認錯人了
Paddi!
懶羊羊
Let's go look somewhere else.
我們再去別的地方找找吧
All right.
好吧
Paddi!
懶羊羊
Paddi, where did you go?
懶羊羊，你去哪了呀？
Could it be that he was captured by Wolffy?
該不會是…被灰太狼抓走了吧？
Don't worry... We will definitely find him.
別擔心…我們肯定能夠找到他的
Just in time.
時間剛剛好
How could he hide and sleep here?
居然躲在這裡睡覺
Weslie, look over there.
喜羊羊，你看那裡
Weather fruits?
天氣果？
995, 996, 997...
995、996、997...
I'm just missing two rain fruits and a wind fruit,
還差兩個雨果一個風果
then the orders are all complete.
訂單就完成了
Everyone will be so surprised when they find out.
大家知道了肯定很驚喜
998, 999...
998、999...
Keep it up, Paddi!
加油啊，懶羊羊
One thousand! Finished!
1000！完成了！
Paddi! You finished all the orders alone.
懶羊羊 你居然一個人完成了所有的訂單
You're amazing!
你太厲害了！
Really? Look!
真的嗎？你們看
I even made such a big wind fruit.
我還做了個這麼大的風果呢
Watch out!
小心啊
Weather fruits!
天氣果
Paddi, don't go over. It's dangerous!
懶羊羊，危險別過去啊
Are you guys okay?
你們沒事吧？
What do we do?
這下該怎麼辦？
What to do? The weather tree won't dry up and die, right?
怎麼辦？天氣樹不會枯死吧？
Don't cry. Take your pills and get better first.
你先別哭了，先吃藥把病治好再說吧
So refreshing!
好清涼啊
I didn't know the cold medicine is this delicious.
原來感冒藥的味道這麼好
If I had known, I would have...
早知道，我…就…
Perfect!
太好了
The weather tree's back to life.
天氣樹恢復生機了
What?
什麼？
How did the weather tree get better all of a sudden?
天氣樹怎麼忽然就變好了？
Good question.
問得好
Those weather fruits exploded, causing a thunderstorm.
由於那些天氣果爆炸 造成了風雨雷電
The dead branches got struck by lightning and fell off coincidentally.
天氣樹的枯枝剛好被雷劈斷
Then the wind blew away the dry leaves.
枯葉被風吹走
The rain fruit coincidentally showered the whole weather tree.
雨果又剛好淋過整棵天氣樹
Thus, the weather tree has been reborn.
所以，天氣樹現在重生了
What a coincidence!
這麼巧
Yes, we're that lucky.
就是這麼巧
I didn't think that I did something good.
真想不到我還立功了
But the 1,000 orders for weather fruits are not done yet.
可是一千個天氣果訂單還沒完成呢
Why am I always the one that suffers?
為什麼受傷的總是我？
TO BE CONTINUED 2775 DAYS FROM SETTING SAIL
（未完待續 距離啟航還剩2775天）